Loot Hello Guide Welcome all of you once
again to their quantity function
and through the team we will talk about the
quarterly results of Loot
You can see that the companies here for
their quarterly results because
I will be discussing this with you through this team
here You can see
whatever value is there in the box,
I will convert it into crores and tell you so that it will be easier for
you to understand and easier for me to
explain it So first of all let's talk about the
total income of the company You can see
that the total income of the company is
very good on both share and air basis and on quarterly basis
because you can see that
last year in the same quarter the
total income of the company was 3058 crores or you
can say 3059 crores and after that the
total income of the company in the last quarter
was 3808 crores and in comparison of these two
you can see that in the
December of current affairs  The total income of the company in the quarter
is 3834, so on both the
bases, here we
can see growth in the income of the company and
if we talk about the expenses of the company, then
you can see that
both of them are bigger than each other, both on year on year basis
and on quarter basis as well. Now let's talk about
profit expansion, then you
can see that on year on
year basis there is a decline in the profit,
and if we talk about year and best then
share and on this, a little growth is
seen here because you can see
that in the last year's quarter the
profit explosion of the company was
approximately 418 crores here, after that
in the last quarter the profit
explosion of the company was approximately 594 crores here
and in the comparison of these two, you
can see that in the December quarter of the current affair, the
profit report of the company is
approximately 421
crores here, so we can send the quarter on year,
here a decline in profit is seen,
but on year on year basis here  But a
little bit of decline is being seen if we
talk about its net profit, then you
can see that Jio has a net profit, there
we get to see a little bit of growth on a year on year basis,
but on a quarterly
basis, there is a decline here,
you can see that the
net profit of the company in the same quarter last year was
approximately 313 crores,
after that the net profit of the company in the last quarter is a
shock of approximately 440 crores or you
can say approximately 40.48 crores and
in comparison of these two, you can see
that the net profit of the company in the December quarter of the current year
is 300.17 crores
or you can say approximately 300.18 crores,
so a decline is being seen in the profit here on a quarterly basis
and the
year old episode is a little bit of a giver here,
you can see that the company has
also given an interim dividend of four rupees to its
investors here, now let's talk about the
running profit, so you see  You
can see that the share which is running on a
quarter to quarter basis and on both year and
test basis, there is a
decline here. Now you can see
that the last GPS
in the SIM quarter was 60.90, after that
in the last quarter the profit was 9.11 and
in the comparison of these two, you can see
that in the December quarter of Current Affairs, there is a
history of space point for seven,
so if we talk about the quarterly results of the company here, then the
quarterly result for the company is good,
it is quite bad because
we do not see much growth here also,
and if we talk about profit, then there is
profit but there is a
decline on a quarterly basis and
even after selling shares and shares, there is not very good growth here,
only here you can see
that the profit of the company is only four crores on a yearly basis,
that is a very good growth
seen here, on a yearly and best and
quarterly basis, there is a huge decline in profit here,
so this is the result of the company's quarter three
Which I shared with you guys here
through this team and if I
share my point here on CR lot then it is almost at
this time 1414 pure skin
level and is updating
and if any dip comes on result basis,
looking at the quantity of the market, then
my feeling is that on long term basis the stock should be
added to your portfolio, the
stock should be given some time, the
stock is quite good, there is
no problem in any way, you can do it in a way, it is a leader in its sector,
okay, so the
company belongs to the insurance sector, so on long
term basis you can
fold the stock and move on, if someone has
made a portion at the higher level, then
move on to a plate at the lower level, this stock can give you
very good returns in the future,
so this is my point feature
which I have shared with you guys here
and when I always tell you guys
that you have to take your own according to yours, you have to
ask your French advisor, you have to do your
own research, here
only I am telling you guys  I also
share information on educational basis and this is what I
always tell you that if you like the video, if you like
that team,
quarter application, this later you are
watching videos, you can subscribe to this channel, like and share this video,
along with subscribing, do press the bell icon
so that you keep getting notifications timely
and as I tell you that if
you have any career related to stock, then
you can ask me by commenting, I
try to
reply to your comment as soon as possible, so that's all you get for now,
in the next team
some other company quarter will get the right result, till then
bye take care